What's wrong?
Did you bite your tongue?
It's my tooth...
It's wobbly...
Don't touch it!
What should I do?
You've got a permanent tooth
coming in from the bottom,
so just leave it alone.
Do you want your rice as porridge?
No, it'll be fine if I eat slowly.
I dunno about tomorrow.
It's different than a sacrifice. Something's off.
I don't think it's like some penalty game.
So, why? I don't get it at all.
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important.
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending.
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I’m with you, I’m happy.
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
Cultural Festival
Daikichi!
Hi.
W-What?!
Look, there's my drawing!
Kaga Rin
Rin-chan, your dad always
comes to these things, huh?
Yeah.
Although he's not my dad...
He's not?!
Huh. It's great.
You know what?!
Rin-chan's the best
at drawing in B Class!
You don't say...
I bet you could become a manga artist!
No way!
I'm sure you could!
Papa!
Over here!
Sorry I'm late.
This guy with the clothes
and the hair is her dad?!
How handsome!
Lucky!
He's so tall!
Know what? Sayaka-chan's father is
31, the same age as you, Daikichi!
Seriously?!
Really? What a happy coincidence.
My papa does modeling!
Wow!
Now, Sayaka!
Just a little.
When I was younger...
I think maybe I've seen you before
in my company's catalog...
Really?!
Excuse me.
If you don't mind my asking,
what's the name of your company?
That may be me!
I'm much obliged!
Cheerful guy, isn't he?
Now I'm embarrassed!
These days, I'm a manager
for the same agency.
Oh, really?
It seems like kind of a waste...
It's the kind of work where you can't
really predict the hours or income,
so when my daughter was
born, I called it a day.
Oh...
At that time, I was drinking like
every night, bitching about work...
Hey, Mi-chan!
Nabe-chin! Long time no see!
We were classmates.
We're both from the neighborhood.
He's got a boy in A Class.
This is Rin-chan's father, Daikichi-san.
He's the same age we are.
Oh yeah? Nice to meet you!
Likewise.
These two are the type
that protect their kids...
Daikichi!
I'm a butcher.
My shop's on the corner
of that shopping street.
Rin and I often get
take-out croquettes there.
Really? That makes me feel good!
Me too! Me too!
I know, I know!
I made fellow father-friends...
In a sense, the world
may be wider here...
Hello.
Hello!
It's suddenly turned cold, hasn't it?
Yes.
It seems the kids are
already in the gym.
I just hope he has his jacket on...
Yeah...
Nitani Kouki
Wow, he's quite the artist.
Really?
I mean, you can tell he
took a lot of time on it...
You know what, all the kids
are in the gym already.
Seriously?!
Crap! My teacher's gonna get mad at me!
Something I don't like about boys...
Oh, how adorable! How many months?
Almost 10 months.
I love babies!
Makes me feel nostalgic...
Well, my kid had the flu last week...
I'm sorry I've kept you...
Oh, really? That must've been rough.
Not at all!
Is it that season already?
With that, they have to stay home for
two days even if the fever's down, right?
So it doesn't spread...
Yeah, but I sent him to school right
after his temperature went down.
Well, what else could you do?
You don't wanna be fired at work.
Right, and he was getting better,
so the virus was probably weakened.
Oh, I'm sure...
Besides, even if he did pass it on,
nobody would ever know who did it.
Shall we go?
Um... What those mothers were
talking about kind of hit home...
And that makes me even more depressed...
Like about work, I can relate...
Yeah, I know...
When it gets cold out, I
become a nervous wreck.
But Kouki, the way he is...
Put your pajamas on now!
But after clearing winter and
it starts getting warm out,
I can finally breathe a sigh of relief.
Daikichi!
Daikichi, I'll go get my
satchel, so wait here!
Are you two dummies?!
Kouki, your nose!
It's cold in the gym, which is why
I told you to wear your jacket!
And don't run in the halls!
Okay!
I said don't run!
Kouki's baby teeth are already
starting to come out, huh?
We live in an apartment complex,
so throwing teeth onto
the roof doesn't work.
Note:
Lower baby teeth are thrown onto the roof as a charm
to make the permanent bottom teeth come in straight
Recently, he doesn't
listen to me at all.
Well, I don't have room to talk...
I used to wear the absolute minimum...
And run down the stairs full speed,
skipping every other step...
I'd wolf down lunch, drink
the milk in one gulp...
It feels really weird telling kids
not to do everything that I did.
You did all that, Daikichi-san?
I think it's relatively
normal for a boy...
Anyway, I don't think of
Kouki as just another kid.
S-Sorry...
But if you were like
that too, Daikichi-san,
it makes me feel a little relieved.
What's wrong? Walk with Kouki!
I don't wanna!
Then let's split into the
boys' team and girls' team!
I don't wanna!
Is Rin-chan's face a little flushed?
I think she's got a fever.
It might get higher.
That's a lot more flushed than usual!
Well, it's not the flu.
For now, please have all of the
family members wear a mask.
Sure!
That's good news, huh?
Yeah!
Huh?
Are you done?
Yeah... I don't feel right here...
The doctor said it was the stomach flu,
so you don't have to force yourself.
Yeah... I feel kind of...
Rin!
W-Washbowl!
Rin does?!
Call an ambulance right away!
No, I already had her checked out
by a doctor and we got medicine,
but she won't take it!
Her fever keeps climbing higher and
she looks like she's miserable...
I bet you had her wear light clothes!
Right now, that's irrelevant!
Did you try mixing the
medicine in with juice?
You always drank it right away if
it was mixed with something sweet.
I'll try it.
Thanks, Mom.
Here, just try a little.
It's sweet.
Come on, just a spoonful.
Daikichi...
I'm sorry for coming so early.
How's Rin-chan?
I'm sorry!
May I come in?
Daikichi, what's with that hair?
Sure...
She doesn't have the flu, but...
Kouki, go watch TV over there.
Yay!
Quietly!
She finally fell asleep
a little while ago...
Her fever keeps rising...
And it seems like she's
not able to sleep much...
She's not sweating at all...
Has she been able to drink?
I was told to at least
give her sports drinks,
but she won't eat or drink anything!
I don't know what to do...
W-What?!
You can't get flustered!
The adult has to stay calm and tell
her it's going to be all right...
It's hard.
I've never seen Rin like that before.
It's not hard! You can do it!
When a child is in real trouble,
an adult who will help
needs to be by their side.
Rin-chan will be fine as long
as you're there, Daikichi-san.
Rin-chan...
Kouki-kun's mom...
You must be thirsty.
Want to try sucking on some ice?
How's that?
It feels good...
Rin! You're up?!
I'm sorry, I was in the bathroom...
Daikichi-san!
Sorry.
In a little while,
suck on some more ice.
Since if you have it all at once,
you'll surprise your tummy...
Okay.
I just put something sweet and
yummy in the fridge for later.
Okay.
I'm sorry. You'll be late
for work, won't you?
Rin-chan is really doing her best.
If you're here for her, she'll
be okay, Daikichi-san.
Right. Thank you...
You too, Kouki, thank you.
Sure.
Sorry. I might have to
take off tomorrow, too.
If something comes up, give me a call.
Gotcha.
Sorry for the trouble...
What are you talkin' about?!
Please, leave everything to me!
Thank you...
Can you eat a little bit?
Yeah...
When you have a cold, you
get to eat all these sweets.
Later.
You'll get better after a bit more rest.
Why Rin?
If I'd gotten it, it'd be nothing to me.
Dammit!
Dammit! Goddammit!
Yeah?
Daikichi!
Hey!
Kouki!
How do you feel, Rin-chan?
Does it hurt anywhere?
I'm okay.
I'm going to make you some
yummy rice gruel now, okay?
Her fever's been up again
since this afternoon...
It's all right.
Even normal temperatures are lower in
the morning and rise from the afternoon.
But it was higher than
39 degrees just before...
Here, put this in the pot.
Sure.
Daikichi...
Water...
That looks good...
I made it for you too, Daikichi-san.
Daikichi! Rin wants water!
Got it!
Kouki, I don't want you catching
it, so stay in this room, okay?
I don't mind getting it.
You can't mean that!
Thanks...
Kouki-kun, thank you.
Kouki, when you're here,
Rin feels totally at ease.
Yeah...
Here, Rin-chan, eat a little bit.
Don't worry. When Kouki gets
sick, he eats this too.
It's specially made gruel that
makes you get better fast.
Kouki-kun too?
That's right...
Whenever he ate this, his cold
was gone before I knew it.
It's good!
Daikichi!
Rin! Are you better?
Yeah. I feel fine.
I'm hungry!
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
Will you tell your mom thank
you for the other evening?
She looked after Rin, so...
Hey, can I go home with you guys?
That again?!
Your mom has to be the one
who picks you up from here!
See, my mom is sick in bed with a cold.
What?! Are you serious?!